Heezen-Tharp collection: Pacific Ocean
Geography and Map Division, Library of Congress
- Series I: Pacific Ocean
  - Group 02 - Pacific Ocean Soundings, 17687458
    - 0334 Oceanic Soundings (Folder Barcode: 00275648255)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 54˚ to 60˚ South and 120˚ to 135˚ East. Royal Australian Navy, Area 498. August 1977.
    - 0335 Oceanic Soundings (Folder Barcode: 00275648255)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 54˚ to 60˚ South and 135˚ to 150˚ East. Royal Australian Navy, Area 499. June 1972.
    - 0336 Oceanic Soundings (Folder Barcode: 00275648255)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 54˚ to 60˚ South and 150˚ to 165˚ East. Royal Australian Navy, Area 500. December 1971.
    - 0337 Oceanic Soundings (Folder Barcode: 00275648255)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 54˚ to 60˚ South and 105˚ to 120˚ East. Royal Australian Navy, Area 521. August 1977.
    - 0338 Oceanic Soundings (Folder Barcode: 00275648255)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 54˚ to 60˚ South and 120˚ to 135˚ East. Royal Australian Navy, Area 522. June 1972.
    - 0339 Oceanic Soundings (Folder Barcode: 00275648255)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 54˚ to 60˚ South and 135˚ to 150˚ East. Royal Australian Navy, Area 523. June 1972.
    - 0340 Oceanic Soundings (Folder Barcode: 00275648255)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 60˚ to 66˚ South and 105˚ to 125˚ East. Royal Australian Navy, Area 542. 1974(?).
    - 0341 Oceanic Soundings (Folder Barcode: 00275648255)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 60˚ to 66˚ South and 125˚ to 145˚ East. Royal Australian Navy, Area 543. February 1972.
    - 0342 Oceanic Soundings (Folder Barcode: 00275648255)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 60˚ to 66˚ South and 145˚ to 165˚ East. Royal Australian Navy, Area 544. March 1974.
    - 0343 Oceanic Soundings (Folder Barcode: 00275648255)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 66˚ to 72˚ South and 125˚ to 150˚ East. Royal Australian Navy, Area 559. June 1972.
    - 0344 Scripps Mid-Pacific Expedition (Folder Barcode: 00275648243)
      a. Paper. b. From 3˚ to 33˚ South and 117˚ to 141˚ West. Worksheet 1.
    - 0345 Scripps Mid-Pacific Expedition (Folder Barcode: 00275648243)
      a. Paper. b. From 3˚ to 19˚ North and 139˚ to 154˚ West. Worksheet 2.
    - 0346 Scripps Mid-Pacific Expedition (Folder Barcode: 00275648243)
      a. Paper. b. From 16˚ to 23˚ North and 158˚ to 178˚ West. Worksheet 3.
    - 0347 Scripps Mid-Pacific Expedition (Folder Barcode: 00275648243)
      a. Paper. b. From 10˚ to 20˚ North and 165˚ East to 178˚ West. Worksheet 4.
    - 0348 Scripps Mid-Pacific Expedition (Folder Barcode: 00275648243)
      a. Paper. b. From 12˚ to 24˚ North and 166˚ East to 170˚ West. Worksheet 5.
    - 0349 Scripps Mid-Pacific Expedition (Folder Barcode: 00275648243)
      a. Paper. b. From 23˚ to 35˚ North and 168˚ West to 168˚ East. Worksheet 6.
    - 0350 Scripps Mid-Pacific Expedition (Folder Barcode: 00275648243)
      a. Paper. b. From 34˚ to 40˚ North and 145˚ to 169˚ West. Worksheet 7.
    - 0351 Scripps Mid-Pacific Expedition (Folder Barcode: 00275648231)
      a. Paper. b. From 39˚ to 41˚ North and 133˚ to 145˚ West. Worksheet 8.
    - 0352 Scripps Mid-Pacific Expedition (Folder Barcode: 00275648231)
      a. Paper. b. From 35˚ to 40˚ North and 129˚ to 135˚ West. Worksheet 9.
    - 0353 Scripps Mid-Pacific Expedition (Folder Barcode: 00275648231)
      a. Paper. b. From 32˚ to 35˚ North and 117˚ to 129˚ West. Worksheet 10.
    - 0354 Robert Conrad 13, Leg 5 (Folder Barcode: 00275648231)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 3˚ to 11˚ South and 151˚ to 153˚ West. Suva to Papeete. February 1970.
    - 0355 Robert Conrad 13, Leg 5 (Folder Barcode: 00275648231)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 12˚ to 18˚ South and 178˚ East to 172˚ West. Suva to Papeete. February 1970.
    - 0356 Robert Conrad 13, Leg 5 (Folder Barcode: 00275648231)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 10˚ to 18˚ South and 149˚ to 152˚ West. Suva to Papeete. February/March 1970.
    - 0357 Eltanin 55 (Folder Barcode: 0027564822A)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 32˚ to 37˚ South and 149˚ to 154˚ East. 2106S and 2107S, sheet 1 of 12.
    - 0358 Eltanin 55 (Folder Barcode: 0027564822A)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 37˚ to 42˚ South and 147˚ to 152˚ East. 2107S and 2207S, sheet 2 of 12.
    - 0359 Eltanin 55 (Folder Barcode: 0027564822A)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 42˚ to 46˚ South and 143˚ to 150˚ East. 2208S, sheet 3 of 12.
    - 0360 Eltanin 55 (Folder Barcode: 0027564822A)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 46˚ to 50˚ South and 148˚ to 150˚ East. 2209S and 2309S, sheet 4 of 12.
    - 0361 Eltanin 55 (Folder Barcode: 0027564822A)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 46˚ to 50˚ South and 130˚ to 138˚ East. 2309S, sheet 5 of 12.
    - 0362 Eltanin 55 (Folder Barcode: 0027564822A)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 42˚ to 46˚ South and 142˚ to 141˚ East. 2308S, sheet 6 of 12.
    - 0363 Eltanin 55 (Folder Barcode: 0027564822A)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 37˚ to 42˚ South and 138˚ to 146˚ East. 2307S and 2308S, sheet 7 of 12.
    - 0364 Eltanin 55 a. Tracing paper. (Folder Barcode: 0027564822A)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 32˚ to 37˚ South and 149˚ to 154˚ East. 30-31 October 1972, sheet 1N of 12.
    - 0365 Eltanin 55 (Folder Barcode: 0027564822A)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 37˚ to 42˚ South and 147˚ to 152˚ East. 1-3 November 1972, sheet 2N of 12.
    - 0366 Eltanin 55 (Folder Barcode: 0027564822A)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 42˚ to 46˚ South and 143˚ to 150˚ East. 4-5 November 1972, sheet 3N of 12.
    - 0367 Eltanin 55 (Folder Barcode: 00275648218)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 46˚ to 50˚ South and 138˚ to 146˚ East. 6-10 November 1972, sheet 4N of 12.
    - 0368 Eltanin 55 (Folder Barcode: 00275648218)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 46˚ to 50˚ South and 130˚ to 138˚ East. 11-13 November 1972, sheet 5N of 12.
    - 0369 Eltanin 55 (Folder Barcode: 00275648218)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 42˚ to 46˚ South and 132˚ to 141˚ East. 14-15 November 1972, sheet 6N of 12.
    - 0370 Eltanin 55 (Folder Barcode: 00275648218)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 37˚ to 42˚ South and 138˚ to 146˚ East. 16-18 November 1972, sheet 7N of 12.
    - 0371 Eltanin 55 (Folder Barcode: 00275648218)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 36˚ to 41˚ South and 136˚ to 146˚ East. 2-8 December 1972, sheet 8N of 12.
    - 0372 Eltanin 55 (Folder Barcode: 00275648218)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 36˚ to 41˚ South and 127˚ to 136˚ East. 9-11 December 1972, sheet 9 of 12.
    - 0373 Eltanin 55 (Folder Barcode: 00275648218)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 36˚ to 41˚ South and 127˚ to 136˚ East. 9-10 December 1972, sheet 9N of 12.
    - 0374 Eltanin 55 (Folder Barcode: 00275648218)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 35˚ to 40˚ South and 117˚ to 127˚ East. 12-16 December 1972.
    - 0375 Eltanin 55 (Folder Barcode: 00275648218)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 35˚ to 40˚ South and 108˚ to 117˚ East. 17-24 December 1972.
    - 0376 Eltanin 55 (Folder Barcode: 00275648218)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 30˚ to 35˚ South and 108˚ to 116˚ East. 25-29 December 1972.
    - 0377 Eltanin 55 (Folder Barcode: 00275648206)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 47˚ to 52˚ South and 147˚ to 152˚ East. 1-3 November 1972. Sheet 2TP of 12.
    - 0378 Eltanin 55 (Folder Barcode: 00275648206)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 42˚ to 46˚ South and 143˚ to 150˚ East. Sheet 3TP of 12.
    - 0379 Eltanin 55 (Folder Barcode: 00275648206)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 46˚ to 50˚ South and 138˚ to 146˚ East. 6-7 November 1972. Sheet 4TP of 12.
    - 0380 Eltanin 55 (Folder Barcode: 00275648206)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 46˚ to 50˚ South and 130˚ to 138˚ East. 11-13 November 1972. Sheet 5TP of 12.
    - 0381 Eltanin 55 (Folder Barcode: 00275648206)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 46˚ to 50˚ South and 132˚ to 141˚ East. 14-15 November 1972. Sheet 6TP of 12.
    - 0382 Eltanin 55 (Folder Barcode: 00275648206)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 37˚ to 42˚ South and 138˚ to 146˚ East. 16-18 November 1972. Sheet 7TP of 12.
    - 0383 Eltanin 55 (Folder Barcode: 0027564819A)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 36˚ to 41˚ South and 136˚ to 146˚ East. 3-7 December 1972. Sheet 8TP of 12.
    - 0384 Eltanin 55 (Folder Barcode: 0027564819A)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 36˚ to 41˚ South and 127˚ to 136˚ East. 9-10 December 1972. Sheet 9TP of 12.
    - 0385 Eltanin 55 (Folder Barcode: 0027564819A)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 35˚ to 40˚ South and 117˚ to 127˚ East. 11-16 December 1972. Sheet 10TP of 12.
    - 0386 Eltanin 55 (Folder Barcode: 0027564819A)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 35˚ to 40˚ South and 108˚ to 117˚ East. 17-24 December 1972. Sheet 11TP of 12.
    - 0387 Eltanin 55 (Folder Barcode: 0027564819A)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 30˚ to 35˚ South and 108˚ to 117˚ East. 25-29 December 1972. Sheet 12TP of 12.
    - 0388 Zapiola-11 (Folder Barcode: 00275648188)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 55˚ to 57˚ South and 60˚ to 66˚ West. Kanves-N15, 1963. a. Ozalid paper. b. From 55˚ to 57˚ South and 60˚ to 66˚ West. Kanves-N15, 1963.
    - 0389 Zapiola-11 (Folder Barcode: 00275648188)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 56˚ to 58˚ South and 50˚ to 60˚ West. Kanves-N16, 1963.
    - 0390 Zapiola-11 (Folder Barcode: 00275648188)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 57˚ to 58˚ South and 40˚ to 50˚ West. Kanves-N17, 1963.
    - 0391 Zapiola-11 (Folder Barcode: 00275648188)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 57˚ to 58˚ South and 30˚ to 40˚ West. Kanves-N18, 1963.
    - 0392 Zapiola-11 (Folder Barcode: 00275648188)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 56˚ to 58˚ South and 26˚ to 30˚ West. Kanves-N19, 1963.
    - 0393 Zapiola-11 (Folder Barcode: 00275648188)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 53˚ to 57˚ South and 22˚ to 27˚ West. Kanves-N20, 1963.
    - 0394 Zapiola-11 (Folder Barcode: 00275648188)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 51˚ to 54˚ South and 20˚ to 30˚ West. Kanves-N21, 1963.
    - 0395 Zapiola-11 (Folder Barcode: 00275648188)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 49˚ to 52˚ South and 15˚ to 20˚ West. Kanves-N22, 1963.
    - 0396 Zapiola-11 (Folder Barcode: 00275648176)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 45˚ to 50˚ South and 6˚ to 15˚ West. Kanves-N23, 1963.
    - 0397 Zapiola-11 (Folder Barcode: 00275648176)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 40˚ to 45˚ South and 4˚ East to 5˚ West. Kanves-N24, 1963.
    - 0398 Zapiola-11 (Folder Barcode: 00275648176)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 35˚ to 41˚ South and 5˚ to 15˚ East. Kanves-N25, 1963.
    - 0399 Zapiola-11 (Folder Barcode: 00275648176)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 33˚ to 36˚ South and 15˚ to 19˚ East. Kanves-N26, 1963.
    - 0400 Zapiola-11 (Folder Barcode: 00275648176)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 34˚ to 36˚ South and 11˚ to 20˚ East. Kanves-N27, 1963.
    - 0401 Zapiola-11 (Folder Barcode: 00275648176)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 35˚ to 38˚ South and 1˚ to 10˚ East. Kanves-N28, 1963.
    - 0402 Zapiola-11 (Folder Barcode: 00275648176)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 37˚ to 39˚ South and 0˚ to 10˚ West. Kanves-N29, 1963.
    - 0403 Zapiola-11 (Folder Barcode: 00275648164)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 38˚ to 39˚ South and 10˚ to 20˚ West. Kanves-N30, 1963.
    - 0404 Zapiola-11 (Folder Barcode: 00275648164)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 38˚ to 40˚ South and 20˚ to 30˚ West. Kanves-N31, 1963.
    - 0405 Zapiola-11 (Folder Barcode: 00275648164)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 39˚ to 40˚ South and 33˚ to 40˚ West. Kanves-N32, 1963.
    - 0406 Zapiola-11 (Folder Barcode: 00275648164)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 38˚ to 40˚ South and 40˚ to 49˚ West. Kanves-N33, 1963.
    - 0407 Zapiola-11 (Folder Barcode: 00275648164)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 36˚ to 39˚ South and 50˚ to 57˚ West. Kanves-N34, 1963.
    - 0408 Zapiola-11 (Folder Barcode: 00275648164)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 38˚ to 39˚ South and 8˚ to 16˚ West. Kanves-N29A, 1963.
    - 0409 Composite Numbers Sheet – West Pacific, North Half (Folder Barcode: 00275648164)
      a. Paper. b. From 30˚ North to 45˚ South
    - 0410 Lamont Ships – Summary Ship of Southern Pacific, East (Folder Barcode: 00275648164)
    - 0411 Soundings Survey by C.S. Recorder – Singapore Strait (Folder Barcode: 00275648152)
      a. Paper. b. From 0˚ to 1˚ 20’ North and 104˚ to 104˚ 30’ East. Singapore to Jesselton. 29 May to 2 June 1962. Sheet 1.
    - 0412 Soundings Survey by C.S. Recorder – Eastern Approaches to the Singapore Strait (Folder Barcode: 00275648152)
      a. Paper. b. From 1˚ to 1˚ 45’ North and 104˚ to 105˚ East. Singapore to Jesselton. 29 May to 2 June 1962. Sheet 2.
    - 0413 Soundings Survey by C.S. Recorder – Anamba Islands (Folder Barcode: 00275648152)
      a. Paper. b. From 1˚ 30’ to 2˚ 30’ North and 105˚ to 107˚ East. Singapore to Jesselton. 29 May to 2 June 1962. Sheet 3.
    - 0414 Soundings Survey by C.S. Recorder – Natuna Islands Passage (Folder Barcode: 00275648152)
      a. Paper. b. From 3˚ to 3˚ 30’ North and 108˚ to 109˚ East. Singapore to Jesselton. 29 May to 2 June 1962. Sheet 5.
    - 0415 Soundings Survey by C.S. Recorder – Sound China Sea Eastern Approaches to the Natuna Islands Passage (Folder Barcode: 00275648152)
      a. Paper. b. From 3˚ 30’ to 4˚ North and 109˚ to 111˚ East. Singapore to Jesselton. 29 May to 2 June 1962. Sheet 6.
    - 0416 Soundings Survey by C.S. Recorder – Southwest of Luconia Shoals (Folder Barcode: 00275648152)
      a. Paper. b. From 4˚ to 5˚ North and 111˚ to 113˚ East. Singapore to Jesselton. 29 May to 2 June 1962. Sheet 7.
    - 0417A Luconia Shelf and North Borneo Trench (Folder Barcode: 00275648152)
      a. Paper. b. From 4˚ to 6˚ North and 113˚ to 115˚ East. Singapore to Jesselton, 29 May to 2 June 1962. Sheet 8.
    - 0417B Soundings Survey by C.S. Recorder – Luconia Shelf (Folder Barcode: 00275648152)
      a. Paper. b. From 4˚ 55’ to 5˚ 15’ North and 113˚ 10’ to 113˚ 37’ East. Singapore to Jesselton, 29 May to 2 June 1962. Sheet 9.
    - 0418 South China Sea – Luconia Shelf (Folder Barcode: 00275648152)
      a. Paper. b. From 5˚ to 5˚ 10’ North and 113˚ 20’ to 113˚ 30’ East. Singapore to Jesselton, 29 May to 2 June 1962. Sheet 10.
    - 0419 South China Sea – Louisa Reef and North Borneo Trench (Folder Barcode: 00275648152)
      a. Paper. b. From 6˚ North and 113˚ to 115˚ East. Singapore to Jesselton, 29 May to 2 June 1962. Sheet 11.
    - 0420 South China Sea – Approaches to Jesselton (Folder Barcode: 00275648152)
      a. Paper. b. From 5˚ 50’ to 6˚ 20’ North and 114˚ 50’ to 116˚ 05’ East. Singapore to Jesselton, Jesselton to Hong Kong. 31 May to 2 June 1962. Sheet 12.
    - 0421 South China Sea – North Borneo, Approaches to Jesselton Cable Landings (Folder Barcode: 00275648152)
      a. Paper. b. From 5˚ 57’ to 6˚ North and 115˚ 59’ to 116˚ 03’ East. 10-13 July 1962. Sheet 13.
    - 0422 South China Sea – Area North of Luconia Shoals (Folder Barcode: 00275648140)
      a. Paper. b. From 6˚ to 6˚ 10’ North and 111˚ to 113˚ East. Jesselton to Singapore. 25-31 July 1962. Sheet 14.
    - 0423 South China Sea – Continental Slope Northeast of the Natuna Islands (Folder Barcode: 00275648140)
      a. Paper. b. From 5˚ 20’ to 6˚ 10’ North and 109˚ to 111˚ East. Jesselton to Singapore. 25-31 July 1962. Sheet 15.
    - 0424 South China Sea –Northeast of Pulo Laut (Natuna Islands) (Folder Barcode: 00275648140)
      a. Paper. b. From 4˚ 40’ to 5˚ 50’ North and 108˚ to 109˚ East. Jesselton to Singapore. 25-31 July 1962. Sheet 16.
    - 0425 Soundings Survey by C.S. Recorder – Outer Approaches to Jesselton (Folder Barcode: 00275648140)
      a. Paper. b. From 6˚ to 7˚ 30’ North and 115˚ to 115˚ 50’ East. Jesselton to Hong Kong. 2 June to 24 July 1962. Sheet 17.
    - 0426 Soundings Survey by C.S. Recorder – Outer Approaches to Jesselton (Folder Barcode: 00275648140)
      a. Paper. b. From 6˚ 20’ to 7˚ 30’ North and 115˚ to 115˚ 50’ East. Jesselton to Hong Kong. 2 June to 24 July 1962. Sheet 17a.
    - 0427 Soundings Survey by C.S. Recorder – Dangerous Ground Passage (Folder Barcode: 00275648140)
      a. Paper. b. From 7˚ 30’ to 9˚ North and 114˚ 40’ to 115˚ 30’ East. Jesselton to Hong Kong. 13 - 24 July 1962. Sheet 18.
    - 0428 Soundings Survey by C.S. Recorder – Dangerous Ground Passage, Middle Portion (Folder Barcode: 00275648140)
      a. Paper. b. From 9˚ to 10˚ 30’ North and 114˚ 40’ to 115˚ 30’ East. Jesselton to Hong Kong. 13 - 24 July 1962. Sheet 19.
    - 0429 Soundings Survey by C.S. Recorder – Seamount East of Eldad Reef (Folder Barcode: 00275648140)
      a. Paper. b. From 10˚ 15’ to 10˚ 30’ North and 114˚ 40’ to 115˚ 12’ East. Jesselton to Hong Kong. 13 - 24 July 1962. Sheet 20.
    - 0430 Soundings Survey by C.S. Recorder – Dangerous Ground Passage, Northern Portion (Folder Barcode: 00275648140)
      a. Paper. b. From 10˚ 30’ to 12˚ North and 115˚ to 115˚ 40’ East. Jesselton to Hong Kong. 13 - 24 July 1962. Sheet 21.
    - 0431 Soundings Survey by C.S. Recorder – Dangerous Ground Passage, Northern Portion (Folder Barcode: 00275648140)
      a. Paper. b. From 10˚ 30’ to 12˚ North and 114˚ 50’ to 115˚ 40’ East. Jesselton to Hong Kong. 13 - 24 July 1962. Sheet 21a.
    - 0432 Soundings Survey by C.S. Recorder – Northern Approaches to Dangerous Ground Passage (Folder Barcode: 00275648140)
      a. Paper. b. From 12˚ to 13˚ 30’ North and 115˚ 30’ to 116˚ East. Jesselton to Hong Kong. 13 - 24 July 1962. Sheet 22.
    - 0433 Soundings Survey by C.S. Recorder – The Abyssal Plain East of Dreyer Bank (Folder Barcode: 00275648140)
      a. Paper. b. From 13˚ 30’ to 15˚ North and 115˚ 40’ to 116˚ 10’ East. Jesselton to Hong Kong. 13 - 24 July 1962. Sheet 23.
    - 0434 South China Sea –Southern Approaches to the Palawan Passage (Folder Barcode: 00275648140)
      a. Paper. b. From 7˚ 30’ to 9˚ North and 115˚ to 117˚ East. Jesselton to Hong Kong. 2 June - July 1962. Sheet 24.
    - 0435 South China Sea –Palawan Passage (Folder Barcode: 00275648140)
      a. Paper. b. From 9˚ to 10˚ 30’ North and 116˚ to 118˚ East. Jesselton to Hong Kong. 2 June – 7 July 1962. Sheet 25.
    - 0436 South China Sea – Northern Approaches to the Palawan Passage (Folder Barcode: 00275648139)
      a. Paper. b. From 10˚ 30’ to 12˚ North and 117˚ 20’ to 118˚ 30’ East. Jesselton to Hong Kong. 2 June – 7 July 1962. Sheet 26.
    - 0437 South China Sea –Palawan Passage Bank (Folder Barcode: 00275648139)
      a. Paper. b. From 10˚ 35’ to 10˚ 53’ North and 117˚ 50’ to 118˚ 26’ East. Jesselton to Hong Kong. 2 June – 7 July 1962. Sheet 27.
    - 0438 South China Sea –Palawan Passage Bank (Contours) (Folder Barcode: 00275648139)
      a. Paper. b. From 10˚ 35’ to 10˚ 55’ North and 117˚ 30’ to 118˚ 25’ East. Jesselton to Hong Kong. 2 June – 7 July 1962. Sheet 27a.
    - 0439 South China Sea – Abyssal Plain, Southern Portion (Folder Barcode: 00275648139)
      a. Paper. b. From 12˚ to 13˚ 30’ North and 116˚ 50’ to 117˚ 40’ East. Jesselton to Hong Kong. 2 June – 7 July 1962. Sheet 28.
    - 0440 South China Sea – Abyssal Plain (Southwest of Scarborough Shoal) (Folder Barcode: 00275648139)
      a. Paper. b. From 13˚ 30’ to 15˚ North and 116˚ 50’ to 117˚ 30’ East. Jesselton to Hong Kong. 2 June – 7 July 1962. Sheet 29.
    - 0441 South China Sea – Abyssal Plain (Vicinity of Truro Shoal) (Folder Barcode: 00275648139)
      a. Paper. b. From 15˚ to 16˚ 30’ North and 116˚ 30’ to 117˚ 30’ East. Jesselton to Hong Kong. 2 June – 7 July 1962. Sheet 30.
    - 0442 South China Sea – Abyssal Plain (Northwest of Truro Shoal) (Folder Barcode: 00275648139)
      a. Paper. b. From 16˚ 30’ to 18˚ North and 116˚ to 117˚ 10’ East. Jesselton to Hong Kong. 2 June – 7 July 1962. Sheet 31.
    - 0443 South China Sea –Recorder Bank (Folder Barcode: 00275648139)
      a. Paper. b. From 16˚ 30’ to 16˚ 50’ North and 116˚ 30’ to 117˚ 08’ East. Jesselton to Hong Kong. 2 June – 7 July 1962. Sheet 32.
    - 0444 South China Sea –Abyssal Plain, Northern Portion (Folder Barcode: 00275648139)
      a. Paper. b. From 18˚ to 19˚ 30’ North and 115˚ 20’ to 116˚ 20’ East. Jesselton to Hong Kong. 2 June – 7 July 1962. Sheet 33.
    - 0445 South China Sea – Continental Slope (Folder Barcode: 00275648139)
      a. Paper. b. From 19˚ 30’ to 21˚ North and 114˚ 30’ to 115˚ 30’ East. Jesselton to Hong Kong. 2 June – 7 July 1962. Sheet 34.
    - 0446 South China Sea – Search for Reported Shoal Southwest of Vereker Bank (Folder Barcode: 00275648139)
      a. Paper. b. From 20˚ 25’ to 20˚ 50’ North and 115˚ 05’ to 115˚ 24’ East. Jesselton to Hong Kong. 2 June – 7 July 1962. Sheet 35.
    - 0447 South China Sea – Continental Shelf (Folder Barcode: 00275648139)
      a. Paper. b. From 21˚ to 22˚ 20’ North and 114˚ 10’ to 115˚ East. Jesselton to Hong Kong. 2 June – 7 July 1962. Sheet 36.
    - 0448 Vema 18 – Station Chart (Folder Barcode: 00275648139)
      a. Paper. b. From 10˚ to 45˚ South and 145˚ to 170˚ East. Wellington to …
    - 0449 Eltanin 44 (Folder Barcode: 00275648127)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 30˚ to 72˚ South and 120˚ East to 150˚ West. Umataka to Maru.
    - 0450 Pacific Soundings (Folder Barcode: 00275648127)
      a. Negative transparency. b. From 2˚ to 3˚ North and 120˚ to 130˚ West. Plotted on BC1301. Vema 32.
    - 0451 Pacific Soundings (Folder Barcode: 00275648127)
      a. Negative transparency. b. From 2˚ to 3˚ North and 110˚ to 120˚ West. Plotted on BC1201. Vema 32.
    - 0452 Pacific Soundings (Folder Barcode: 00275648127)
      a. Negative transparency. b. From 2˚ to 3˚ North and 130˚ to 140˚ West. 1401N. Vema 24 and 32.
    - 0453 Pacific Soundings (Folder Barcode: 00275648127)
      a. Negative transparency. b. From 1˚ to 3˚ North and 140˚ to 144˚ West. 1501N. Vema 24 and 32.
    - 0454 Pacific Soundings (Folder Barcode: 00275648127)
      a. Negative transparency. b. From 13˚ to 108˚ West. 1101N. Vema 21 and 32.
    - 0455 Pacific Soundings (Folder Barcode: 00275648127)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 23˚ to 27˚ North and 65˚ to 66˚ West. 0705N. Sheet D.
    - 0456 Vema 18 – Soundings (Folder Barcode: 00275648127)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 11˚ to 15˚ South and 160˚ to 170˚ West. Samoa to Tahiti. Extensive annotation and notes.
    - 0457 Vema 18 – Soundings (Folder Barcode: 00275648127)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 30˚ to 34˚ North and 64˚ to 69˚ West.
    - 0458A-C Soundings From the Sea of Okhotsk to New Guinea (Folder Barcode: 00275648127)
      a. Positive transparency. b. From 10˚ to 60˚ North and 110˚ to 165˚ East. Composite of 3 transparencies.
    - 0459 Wellington Harbor (Folder Barcode: 00275648127)
      a. Negative print. b. From 41˚ 13’ to 41˚ 20’ South and 174˚ 45’ to 174˚ 55’East. Data from Vema 18.
    - 0460 Konokioeki Site Survey (Folder Barcode: 00275648127)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 10˚ to 14˚ North and 156˚ to 161˚ East. Hawaii to Ontag Java Plateau. May, June, and August 1971.
    - 0461 Konokioeki Site Survey (Folder Barcode: 00275648115)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 0˚ to 3˚ North and 159˚ 30’ Plateau. May, June, and August 1971.
    - 0462 Pacific Soundings (Folder Barcode: 00275648115)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 30˚ South to 30˚ North and 60˚ to 150˚ West. PDR and Scripps data – summary sheet.
    - 0463 Pacific Soundings (Folder Barcode: 00275648115)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 9˚ to 14˚ North and 115˚ to 160˚ East. Covers 2102N and 2103N.
    - 0464 Profile – P103 S (Folder Barcode: 00275648115)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 40˚ to 50˚ South and 170˚ to 180˚ East.
    - 0465A-D Eltanin 15 Soundings (Folder Barcode: 00275648115)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 55˚ to 56˚ South and 129˚ to 131˚ West. Composite of 4 sheets.
    - 0466 Profile 693 (Folder Barcode: 00275648115)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 40˚ to 50˚ South and 165˚ East to 175˚ West.
    - 0467 Pacific Soundings (Folder Barcode: 00275648115)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 35˚ to 55˚ South and 155˚ East to 170˚ West.
    - 0468 Pacific Soundings (Folder Barcode: 00275648115)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 30˚ to 50˚ South and 120˚ to 160˚ East. Poorly plotted data.